<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sunhacks-Patch1</string>
    <string name="the_gateway_of_india_is_an_arch_monument_built_in_the_early_20th_century_in_the_city_of_bombay_mumbai_india_it_was_erected_to_commemorate_the_landing_of_king_emperor_george_v_the_first_british_monarch_to_visit_india_in_december_1911_at_strand_road_near_wellington_fountain">The Gateway of India is an arch-monument built in the early 20th century in the city of Bombay (Mumbai), India. It was erected to commemorate the landing of King-Emperor George V, the first British monarch to visit India, in December 1911 at Strand Road near Wellington Fountain.</string>
    <string name="the_taj_mahal_is_located_on_the_right_bank_of_the_yamuna_river_in_a_vast_mughal_garden_that_encompasses_nearly_17_hectares_in_the_agra_district_in_uttar_pradesh_it_was_built_by_mughal_emperor_shah_jahan_in_memory_of_his_wife_mumtaz_mahal_with_construction_starting_in_1632_ad_and_completed_in_1648_ad_with_the_mosque_the_guest_house_and_the_main_gateway_on_the_south_the_outer_courtyard_and_its_cloisters_were_added_subsequently_and_completed_in_1653_ad">The Taj Mahal is located on the right bank of the Yamuna River in a vast Mughal garden that encompasses nearly 17 hectares, in the Agra District in Uttar Pradesh. It was built by Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan in memory of his wife Mumtaz Mahal with construction starting in 1632 AD and completed in 1648 AD, with the mosque, the guest house and the main gateway on the south, the outer courtyard and its cloisters were added subsequently and completed in 1653 AD.</string>
    <string name="the_taj_mahal_is_located_on_the_right_bank_of_the_yamuna_river_in_a_vast_mughal_garden_that_encompasses_nearly_17_hectares_in_the_agra_district_in_uttar_pradesh_it_was_built_by">The Taj Mahal is located on the right bank of the Yamuna River in a vast Mughal garden that encompasses nearly 17 hectares, in the Agra District in Uttar Pradesh. It was built by</string>
    <string name="the_gateway_of_india_is_an_arch_monument_built_in_the_early_20th_century_in_the_city_of_bombay_mumbai_india">The Gateway of india is an arch-monument built in the early 20th century in the city of Bombay Mumbai India</string>
    <string name="redfort">Red Fort</string>
    <string name="chittogarh">Chittorgarh</string>
    <string name="gateway">Gateway</string>
    <string name="tajmahal">Taj Mahal</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="red_fort_also_called_lal_qal_ah_also_spelled_lal_kila_or_lal_qila_mughal_fort_in_old_delhi_india_it_was_built_by_shah_jah_n_in_the_mid_17th_century_and_remains_a_major_tourist_attraction">Red Fort, also called Lal Qalʿah, also spelled Lal Kila or Lal Qila, Mughal fort in Old Delhi, India. It was built by Shah Jahān in the mid-17th century and remains a major tourist attraction.</string>
    <string name="the_chittorgarh_literally_chittor_fort_also_known_as_chittod_fort_is_one_of_the_largest_forts_in_india_it_is_a_unesco_world_heritage_site_the_fort_was_the_capital_of_mewar_and_is_located_in_the_present_day_city_of_chittorgarh">The Chittorgarh (literally Chittor Fort), also known as Chittod Fort, is one of the largest forts in India. It is a UNESCO World Heritage Site. The fort was the capital of Mewar and is located in the present-day city of Chittorgarh.</string>
</resources>